legavenue.com 2016-11-28

# Privacy Policy | Leg Avenue

**Effective as of January 1, 2014**  
  
---  
  
**Your Privacy and the Security of Your Personal Information is Very Important to Us**

Leg Avenue, Inc. (“Leg Avenue”) values our customers and visitors to this website and respect your concerns about the privacy of your personal information and data security. Our Privacy and Security Policy (the "Privacy Policy") is intended to protect your privacy and provide you with a safe and secure shopping experience. This Privacy Policy applies to www.legavenue.com (the "Website"). This Privacy Policy protects consumers providing information through our Website and is not designed to protect business information. By using our Website you consent to the collection and use of your personal information. In addition to reviewing our Privacy Policy, you should also read our Terms of Use for our Website. Your use of our Website constitutes your agreement to its terms and conditions.  
  
**Our Privacy Policy Will Change Over Time  **

Because we continue to develop our Website and take advantage of technologies to improve the services we provide, our policies will change over time. We encourage you to refer to this Privacy Policy from time to time to stay abreast of our most current privacy policy practices. If you are a registered user of our Website, we may notify you by email of material changes to our Privacy Policy using the most current email address you have provided to us. Your continued access and use of our Website will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to our Privacy Policy.  
  
**Summary of Our Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy explains and summarizes how we collect, use and protect your personal information as you interact with us online and through our customer and technical support. This Privacy Policy explains:

  * What information Leg Avenue gathers from users of our Website.
  * How Leg Avenue uses the personal information that you share with us and that we learn about you because of our relationship.
  * How Leg Avenue uses "cookies" and "IP Addresses."
  * What personal information, if any, Leg Avenue may share about you with others and the conditions that protect your information if it must be shared.
  * What kind of security measures Leg Avenue takes to protect your information from loss or disclosure and how Leg Avenue will inform you in the event of a security breach.
  * The circumstances under which you can access your personal information you have shared with Leg Avenue and have that information corrected, restrict Leg Avenue’s use of that information, and even have it removed from our records.

**The Type of Information our Website Collects  **

Leg Avenue collects information that you provide to us or that we learn about you from your use of our Website. We receive and store information you enter on our Website or give to us in any other way. For example, you may provide information to us when you register with our Websites, sign-in, search, add items to your shopping cart, pay for an item, participate in a survey, contest or promotion, request to receive our marketing materials, or communicate with Leg Avenue’s customer service. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, phone number, email address, payment card information, and personal shopping and product preferences.   
We also automatically receive and store certain types of information whenever you visit our Websites. We might also receive information about you from other sources, such as in providing you special offers that we think will be of interest, and we may add that information to our account information. 

We use a third-party service provider to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet and sometimes on this site. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our Website, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other Websites to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major websites. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. They do not know the name, phone number, address, email address, or any personally identifying information about the user.  **If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this anonymous information used by our third party service provider.**

We do not respond to ‘do not track’ signals or similar mechanisms. Third-party service providers keep track of your browsing activities on our Websites, which enable us to target advertising based on your browsing history and preferences. You can learn more about online marketing practices and the technologies that support them, or opt-out of third party tracking mechanisms by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative website.  
  
Our social media tools, such as the Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, Instagram, and Pinterest, widgets, are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Website. Your activity with these tools is governed by the privacy policies of the companies that provide them.  
  
**How Leg Avenue Uses Information About You**

We use information we have collected about you to provide you with the very best shopping experience, the most current fashion clothing and accessories, and personal style news.  **We do not sell your personal information to third parties for any reason.**  We do not disclose your personal information to unaffiliated third parties, or to our affiliates, who may want to offer you their own products and services unless you have requested or authorized us to do so.

We may share your personal information with third parties or affiliates of Leg Avenue where it is necessary for us to complete a transaction you authorized or perform some other activity you have asked us to do.

We may share your personal information with third parties or affiliates of Leg Avenue with whom we have contracted to perform services on our behalf. All companies that act on our behalf are contractually obligated to keep the personal information we provide to them confidential and to use the personal information we share only to provide the services we ask them to perform. 

We may disclose personal information about our customers as permitted or required by law, such as in connection with a subpoena or similar legal process, or in connection with a merger, acquisition or bankruptcy, as discussed further below. We may disclose information about you to protect against fraud and other crimes and to enforce our contracts with you. 

We try to provide you with the information you need to make informed reasonable choices with respect to how our Website uses or shares your information. Leg Avenue collects and uses personal information from you in several ways:

  * **Website usage.**  Leg Avenue or Leg Avenue’s authorized service providers may observe activities, preferences and transactional data (such as your IP address, browser type and operating system) relating to your use of our Website. We may use this collected or logged information in order to provide better service, to facilitate our customers' use of the Website, to track usage of the Website, and to address security hazards. Leg Avenue, or one of Leg Avenue’s authorized service providers, may use this information to track aggregate traffic patterns throughout our Website for Leg Avenue’s internal analysis.

  * **Online Transactions.  **We collect information about you when you shop on our Website. You may visit our Website without registering, but if you wish to add merchandise to your shopping cart, create a wish list or use other special features offered on our Website, you will need to provide us with certain information, including your name, address, phone number and email address, to open an account with us. We will assist you in creating a user id and a password to protect your account information.

**Our Security Practices**

Our internal data security policies restrict access to customers' personal information to authorized employees. Authorized employees may use our customers' personal information for Leg Avenue business purposes only. Our employees are bound by Leg Avenue policies that require them to maintain the confidentiality of our customers' personal information. Employees who violate these requirements are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination.

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that are designed to guard our customers' personal information. For example, for the security of your online visit to our Website, we may make use of firewall barriers, encryption techniques and/or authentication procedures. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be absolutely secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Leg Avenue cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. In the event of a breach of the confidentiality or security of your personal information, we will notify you as necessary and to the extent possible so you can take appropriate protective steps. Unless you indicate otherwise, we may notify you under such circumstances using the email address you provided to us when you registered with our Website.  
  
**What are Cookies and How Does our Websites Use Them?  
**  
We may use "cookies" to collect or log certain information. A cookie is a small piece of information that a website stores on a personal computer and which it can later retrieve. We may use cookies for some administrative purposes, for example, to store our customers' preferences for certain kinds of products or to store a password so that you do not have to input it every time you visit our website. The cookies will not contain information that will enable anyone to contact our customers via telephone, email, or any other means. If our customers are uncomfortable with the use of cookie technology, they can set their browsers to refuse cookies. Certain of our services, however, could be dependent on cookies and our customers may disable those services by refusing cookies.  
  
**Links to Third Party Sites and Websites Containing our Websites Branding**

Our Websites may contain links to third party sites. Please be aware, however, that Leg Avenue is not responsible for and cannot control the privacy policies of these other sites or their practices. We encourage you to read the privacy policies for these other sites, as they may differ from ours. This Privacy Policy applies solely to personal information collected by Leg Avenue.  
  
**Contact Preferences and Accessing Your Personal Information  **

You have choices when it comes to how Leg Avenue uses your personal information. When you register online with our Website you can choose not to receive information about merchandise, services and special promotional offers from us by direct mail and/or email. If you elect not to receive such product marketing information by direct mail or email, Leg Avenue may continue to contact you as necessary to service your account and process your transactions. You can change your preferences by following the instructions for opting out at the end of the marketing email, or by following the instructions for Account Information on the Website or by contacting Customer Service at www.legavenue.com/contacts, or calling in the U.S. or Canada  1-888-453-4283 (4LEGAVE) (Toll Free).

Keeping your account information accurate and up to date is very important so we can provide you with excellent service. If your account information is incomplete, inaccurate or not current, please follow the instructions for My Account on our Website to correct or update your account information online, or you may contact Customer Service at www.legavenue.com/contacts, or call in the U.S. or Canada 1-888-453-4283 (4LEGAVE) (Toll Free).

If you need additional assistance or wish more information about our privacy practices, please call in the U.S. or Canada 1-888-453-4283 (4LEGAVE) (Toll Free).  
  
**This Privacy Policy applies to U.S. and Canadian Customers**

Our Website is hosted in the United States and is intended for United States and Canadian visitors.

This Privacy Policy applies to customer relationships established in the United States and Canada. Parts of this Privacy Policy may not apply to visitors outside the United States and Canada. Like almost every website, our Website may be accessed by an international audience. If you are a non-U.S. visitor to our Website, by visiting our Website and providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that your personal information may be processed for the purposes identified in this Privacy Policy. In addition, such data may be stored on servers located in the United States, which may have less stringent privacy practices than those your own resident jurisdiction. By providing us with your data, you consent to transfer of such data.  
  
**Mergers, Acquisitions and Bankruptcy**

If Leg Avenue should ever file for bankruptcy or merge with another company, or if Leg Avenue should decide to buy another business, or sell or reorganize part or all of Leg Avenue’s business, Leg Avenue may be required to disclose your personal information to prospective or actual purchasers and other parties. It is Leg Avenue’s practice to obtain appropriate protections for information disclosed in these types of transactions. Leg Avenue cannot, however, guarantee that Leg Avenue’s Privacy Policy will remain unchanged if Leg Avenue is sold or merges with another company.  
  
**Our Websites are Not for Use by Children**

Children are not eligible to use our Website. We ask that minors (under the age of 18) only use our Website in conjunction with their parents or guardians. Children under 13 years of age should not send any information about themselves to Leg Avenue. If a child under 13 submits information through any part of our Website, and Leg Avenue becomes aware that the person submitting the information is a child, we will attempt to delete this information as soon as possible. Because we do not knowingly collect any personal information about children under 13, we do not use or disclose such information to third parties.  
  
**What else should I know about my privacy?**

You should be careful to maintain the secrecy of your passwords and/or account information and be responsible about protecting your personal information and identity whenever you are online.  

 **Trademark Notice**

Leg Avenue®,  Skinny Dip®, Sexy Mannequin®, Industrial Net®, Enchanted Costumes by Leg Avenue®, Leg Avenue®,  Wonderland Costumes by Leg Avenue®, Adventureland Costumes by Leg Avenue®,  **Leg Avenue**  ™, and Inventors of Fantasy™, are tradenames and/or trademarks of Leg Avenue, Inc. and its affiliates.

Leg Avenue.com     

Leg Avenue, Inc.  
19601 East Walnut Drive South 

City of Industry, CA 91748  
626-581-1273 (office)  
626-737-1114 (fax)
